BECKY POLLARD

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT

I'm a developer with 2 years of experience, working primarily in front-end but hoping to expand my stack to include back-end skills. I create engaging and beautiful digital experiences, with focus on the human impact of tech and accessibility.

CONTACT

Toronto, Ontario

hello@beckypollard.com www.beckypollard.com www.linkedin.com/in/becky-pollard

EXPERIENCE

Uberflip

Software Developer // April 2019 - May 2020 Front End Developer // April 2019 - April 2020

GroupBy Inc

Front-End Developer // August 2018 - March 2019

Canada Learning Code

Mentor // April 2018 - March 2019

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology (HackerYou)

Web Development Immersive // 2018

Humber Institute of Technology and Advanced Learning

Certificate in Web Design, Dev, & Maintenance // 2016 - 2017

Fanshawe College of Applied Arts and Technology

Advanced Diploma in Graphic Design // 2012 - 2015

SKILLS SAMPLE

- // HTML5
- // CSS3 & SCSS
- // JavaScript & jQuery & React
- // Webpack & Gulp
- // Technical Documentation
- // Web Accessibility
- // Git & GitHub

- // Responsive Design
- // Web Best Practices
- // Browser compatibility
- // Adobe Photoshop

// Adobe Illustrator

+ more!

- // Vector and SVG creation
- // Image manipulation